​​​ ​Takedown, takedown Takedown, down, down, down ​ ​​
​​​ ​Takedown, takedown​ ​​
​​ ​(HUNTR/X girls to the world)​ ​​
​​​ ​Takedown, down, down, down​ ​​
​​​ ​(it's a takedown)​ ​​
​​ ​Takedown, down, down, down​ ​​
​​​ ​So sweet, so easy on the eyes, but hideous on the inside​ ​​
​​​ ​Whole life spreadin' lies, but you can't hide, baby, nice try​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm 'bout to switch up these vibes, I finally opened my eyes​ ​​
​​​ ​It's time to kick you straight back into the night​ ​​
​​​ ​'Cause I see your real face, and it's ugly as sin​ ​​
​​​ ​Time to put you in your place 'cause you're rotten within​ ​​
​​​ ​When your patterns start to show​ ​​
​​​ ​It makes the hatred wanna grow outta my veins​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't think you're ready for the takedown​ ​​
​​​ ​Break you into pieces in a world of pain 'cause you're all the same​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, it's the takedown​ ​​
​​​ ​A demon with no feelings don't deserve to live​ ​​
​​​ ​It's so obvious​ ​​
​​​ ​I'ma gear up and take you down (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down)​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a takedown (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down)​ ​​
​​​ ​I'ma take it down   (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down)​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a takedown, I'ma take you out, you'll break down like, "What?"​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a takedown, I'ma take you out, and it ain't gonna stop​ ​​
​​​ ​정신을 놓고, 널 짓밟고, 칼을 새겨놔​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll be beggin' and cryin', all of you dyin', never miss my shot​ ​​
​​​ ​When your patterns start to show​ ​​
​​​ ​It makes the hatred wanna grow outta my veins​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't think you're ready for the takedown​ ​​
​​​ ​당당하게 어둠 앞에 다가서, 다 무너뜨려​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, it's the takedown​ ​​
​​​ ​A demon with no feelings don't deserve to live​ ​​
​​​ ​It's so obvious​ ​​
​​​ ​I'ma gear up and take you down (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down)​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a takedown (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down)​ ​​
​​​ ​(watch me do it, yeah)​ ​​
​​ ​I'ma take it down (woah-oh, da-da-da, down)​ ​​
​​​ ​(ooh, ooh)​ ​​
​​ ​It's a takedown (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down)​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, you're the master of illusion​ ​​
​​​ ​나를 속이려 하지 마​ ​​
​​​ ​Look at all the masses that you're foolin'​ ​​
​​​ ​But they'll turn on you soon, so how?​ ​​
​​​ ​How can you sleep or live with yourself?​ ​​
​​​ ​A broken soul trapped in the nastiest shell​ ​​
​​​ ​영혼 없는 네 목숨을 끊으러, and watch you die-ie-ie​ ​​
​​​ ​You can try, but you can't hide​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a takedown, I'ma take you out, you'll break down like, "What?"​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a takedown, I'ma take you out, and it ain't gonna stop​ ​​
​​​ ​I'ma cut you open, lose control, then rip out your heart​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll be beggin' and cryin', all of you dyin'​ ​​
​​​ ​I'ma gear up and take you down (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down)​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a takedown (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down)​ ​​
​​​ ​(yeah-yeah, yeah-yeah)​ ​​
​​ ​It's a takedown (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down)​ ​​
​​​ ​(yeah)​ ​​
​​ ​I'ma take it down (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down)​ ​​
​​​ ​I'ma take it down (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down)​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a takedown (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down) ​ ​​
​​​ ​(ooh)​ ​​
​​ ​It's a takedown (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down) ​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a takedown (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down) ​ ​​
​​​ ​(watch me do it, yeah)​ ​​
​​ ​It's a takedown (whoa-oh, da-da-da, down) ​ ​​
​​​ ​Take it down​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you for listening!​ ​​